Finding Aid for John Engler Papers, 1968-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Gubernatorial Papers, 1970-2003; 411 linear feet
  - Legislative Affairs Division, 1991-2002; 39.3 linear feet
    - Public Acts and Vetoes, 2002; 7.1 linear feet (Box 273)
      - Public Laws of, 2002; 125 folders (Box 276)
        (nos. 311-435)
      - Public Laws of, 2002; 90 folders (Box 277)
        (nos. 436-525)
      - Public Laws of, 2002; 95 folders (Box 278)
        (nos. 526-620)
      - Public Laws of, 2002; 120 folders (Box 279)
        (nos. 621-740)
      - Public Laws of, 2002; 8 folders (Box 280)
        (nos. 741-747)
      - Vetoed
        - HB 4022, 3/15/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 4990, 7/23/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 5103, 7/9/2002 (Box 280)
        - SB 117, 7/25/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 4647, 11/27/2002 (Box 280)
        - SB 437, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - SB 1398, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - SB 576, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - SB 1353, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - SB 638, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 5977, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 5978, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 5952, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - SB 11, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 4017, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 6120, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 5467, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 5523, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
        - HB 5291, 12/30/2002 (Box 280)
    - JE Issues
      - 1992-2002, 0.2 linear feet (Box 280)
        This expandable file contains Engler's handwritten comments on the process of making particular laws--suggesting exchanges and compromises and delineating the issues on which he would refuse to concede. It includes Engler's handwritten editions of the Public Airport Authority Act (2002) and the Distressed Communities Economic Development Authority Act (2002).
  - Campaigns, Inaugurations, Special Projects (Operations Division), 1971-1990; 1987-1999; 33.7 linear feet
    This series of political materials contains documents transferred by Nancy Harrison, the Director of the Operations Division, arranged by campaign or project, roughly chronologically. Some campaign records received from the External (Public) Affairs office are also consolidated here. Researchers interested in George W. Bush's 2000 campaign in Michigan should consult the "Executive Office--Governor's Own Office--George W. Bush Presidential Campaign" subseries.
    - Engler for Governor, 1990; 1971-1990; 5.6 linear feet
      Within the "Engler for Governor 1990" subseries, the "Candidacy Research" files contain interesting material. Prior to mounting his campaign, John Engler, John Kost of the Michigan Senate Majority Office and Jill Murphy executed an intensive research project to document Engler's political history, compiling his votes and speeches in the legislature, and his press coverage. They also researched Engler's potential opponents for the Republican nomination.
      - Endorsements and Questionnaires, Anne Armstrong-Cusak, 1990; 1.2 linear feet
        - JME Endorsements, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Association Lists/Records, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Endorsement Rejects, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Health, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Questionnaire Background, 1990 (Box 281)
        - American Automobile Association (AAA), 1990 (Box 281)
        - American Freedom Coalition, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Associated Builders and Contractors, Inc. (ABC) West Michigan Chapter, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Associated Newspapers, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Association for Retarded Citizens (ARC) of Oakland County Political Forum, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Auburn Argus, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Big Rapids Pioneer, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Citizens Against Airport Development (CAAD), 1990 (Box 281)
        - Coalition of Michigan Sportsmen, 1990 (Box 281)
        - College of Emergency Physicians, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Crime Prevention Association of Michigan, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Dearborn Business and Professional Women, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Detroit Area Business and Professional Exchange, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Detroit Free Press, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Detroit News, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Detroit Rotary Club, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Dow Chemical Political Action Committee (PAC), 1990 (Box 281)
        - First Assembly of God, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Flint Area Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Friends of the Land of Keweenaw (FOLK), 1990 (Box 281)
        - Genesee County Chapter Michigan Townships Association (MTA), 1990 (Box 281)
        - GMI Engineering & Management Institute, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Groundwork, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Guide to Congress, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Hospital Association PAC, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Huron Valley Physicians Association, PC, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Judicial Conferences, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Lakes Area Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Lansing Business Forum, 1990 (Box 281)
        - League of Conservation Voters, 1990 (Box 281)
        - League of Women Voters, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Lenawee County Board of Realtors, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Manchester Journal, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Mental Health Coalition, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association for Counseling and Development, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of Ambulance Services, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of Clerks Summer Conference, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of Community Mental Health Boards, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of Counties, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of Fire Chiefs, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of Home Builders, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of Manufactured Homes, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of Professional Insurance Agents, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of Public Health, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of Realtors, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Association of School Administrators, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Bear and Wine Wholesalers, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Bikers Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Chiropractic Society, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Committee for Freedom, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Decency Action Council, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Farm Bureau AGRIPAC Incumbent/Non-incumbent, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Farmers Hall of Fame, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Federation of Private Child and Family Agencies, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Grocers Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Hospital Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Insurance Federation, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Kiwanis, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Library Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Manufacturers' Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Municipal League, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Nature Conservancy, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Non-Profit Forum, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Nursery and Landscape Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Pharmacist Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Psychiatric Society, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Public Employee Local UAW 6000, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Restaurant Association (MRA), 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Retailers Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Sheriffs Association, 1989-1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan State Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan State Medical Society (MSMS), 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan Township Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Michigan United Conservation Clubs (MUCC), 1990 (Box 281)
        - Mid-America Economic Development Council, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Morning Sun, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Mothers Against Drunk Driving (MADD), 1990 (Box 281)
        - Mount Pleasant Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Muskego Community College, 1990 (Box 281)
        - National Association of Women Business Owners, 1990 (Box 281)
        - National Federation of Independent Businesses, 1990 (Box 281)
        - National Rifle Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - New Prospect Baptist Church, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Northern Michigan Schools Legislative Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Osteopath Groups, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Prosecuting Attorneys Association, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Right to Life Michigan PAC, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Right to Life Lifespan of Metro Detroit, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Sanilac County News, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Senior Power Day Platform, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Sheet Metal and Air Conditioning Contractors National Association (SMACNA), 1990 (Box 281)
        - Small Biz PAC, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Small Business Association of Michigan (SBAM), 1990 (Box 281)
        - South Haven Tribune, 1990 (Box 281)
        - Southeast Michigan Builders' Association, 1990 (Box 282)
        - State Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Task Forces, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Total Therapy Management, Inc., 1990 (Box 282)
        - Township Times, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Traverse City Board of Realtors, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Traverse City Record Eagle, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Upper Peninsula Environmental Coalition, 1990 (Box 282)
        - US-131 Area Development Association, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Up North, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Veterans/Paralyzed Veterans, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Vocational Agricultural, undated (Box 282)
        - Watershed Council, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Western Michigan Educators, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Westland Chambers, 1990 (Box 282)
        - West Michigan Environmental Action Council, 1990 (Box 282)
        - White Lake Beacon, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Women Active in Muskegon PAC, 1990 (Box 282)
        - Women's Assembly, 1990 (Box 282)
      - Schedules, 1990; 2 linear feet
        - January-July 1990, 17 folders (Box 282)
        - August-December 1990, 16 folders (Box 283)
        - Surrogate's Schedules, Sep.-October 1990; 2 folders (Box 283)
        - Surrogate's Schedules, (cont.), Sep.-October 1990; 2 folders (Box 284)
        - Campaign Events Sorted by County, A-L, 1990; 2 folders (Box 284)
      - Press Officer John Truscott, 1987-1990; 1.8 linear feet
        - AIDS, 1988-1989 (Box 284)
        - American Legislative Exchange Council (ALEC), 1987 (Box 284)
        - BABES Alive (Beginning Alcohol & Addictions Basic Education Studies), 1988 (Box 284)
        - Ballot Proposal B, 1988 (Box 284)
        - Binsfeld Tax Returns, 1987-1989 (Box 284)
        - Blanchard Negative Ads, 1990 (Box 284)
        - Campaign Brochures, 1990 (Box 284)
        - "Captive Nations" Speech (Latvia, Lithuania, and Estonia), 1990 (Box 284)
        - Child Care Task Force, undated (Box 284)
        - Crandall, Nancy, 1988 (Box 284)
        - Cruce, Doug, 1988 (Box 284)
        - Declaration of Candidacy for Governor, February 12, 1990 (Box 284)
        - Drug Testing in the Workplace, 1987-1988 (Box 284)
        - Drugs Task Force, 1989 (Box 284)
        - Drunk Driving Task Force, 1989; 2 folders (Box 284)
        - Dunn, Jim, 1988 (Box 284)
        - Education, 1987-1988 (Box 284)
        - Education Reform, 1990 (Box 284)
        - "Educational Quality in the 21st Century" Michigan School Finance Committee, 1987 (Box 284)
        - Edwards, F. Robert, 1988 (Box 284)
        - Environment/Conservation, 1990 (Box 284)
        - Fifty-six Newsletter, 1988 (Box 284)
        - File of written work, 1987-1989 (Box 284)
          (Work for the Michigan Senate.)
        - Film Days
          (Film Day files contain releases from subjects.)
          - Mt. Pleasant, Ithaca, and Caro, October 6-8, 1989 (Box 284)
          - Detroit, December 20, 1989 (Box 284)
          - Beal City, Mt. Pleasant, March 23-25, 1990 (Box 284)
            (Contains photos of film sites)
          - Dearborn and Detroit, April 21, 1990 (Box 284)
          - Lansing, Flint, Midland, Mt. Pleasant, Grand Rapids, Traverse City, and Detroit, May 18-21, 1989 (Box 284)
        - Fitzgerald, Frank, 1989 (Box 284)
        - Grass Roots Report/Leadership Update, 1989-1990 (Box 284)
        - Guyer, Gordon, 1988 (Box 284)
        - Happy Pack List, 1989-1990 (Box 284)
          (Recipients of Engler Campaign Newsletter)
        - Heartland Institute, 1987-1988 (Box 285)
        - Hillegonds, Paul, 1988 (Box 285)
        - Johnny Engler's Top 40 Birthday Celebration--Media, 1988 (Box 285)
        - "Leading the Way to a Winning Campaign: 1986 Elections Manual Candidates and Campaign Operators," by Michigan Republican State Committee, E. Spencer Abraham, 1986 (Box 285)
        - Legislative Explorers, 1989 (Box 285)
        - Letters to the Editor, 1990 (Box 285)
        - Mackinac Island Republican Leadership Conference, September 22-24, 1989 (Box 285)
        - Mason, Randy, 1988 (Box 285)
        - Media Coverage of the House Republican Task Force on Illegal Drugs, 1989 (Box 285)
        - Media Guide, circa 1989 (Box 285)
          (List of media outlets and contacts by jurisdiction of Republican Michigan Legislators)
        - Media Lists, 1990 (Box 285)
        - Media Thank-yous and Requests, 1989 (Box 285)
        - Michigan Association of Home Builders, 1990 (Box 285)
        - "Michigan Beyond 2000," by the Hudson Institute for the Michigan Senate, 1985 (Box 285)
        - Michigan Black Press Association, 1990 (Box 285)
        - Michigan Educational Trust, 1988 (Box 285)
        - Michigan Manufacturers Association Lawyers Committee, 1988 (Box 285)
        - Moped Forum, 1987 (Box 285)
        - Nye, Michael, 1988-1989 (Box 285)
        - Ouwinga, Sid, 1988 (Box 285)
        - "Political Resources in a Campaign for State Representative: John M. Engler -- 100th District," by Richard E. Posthumus, Political Science 490, Mr. Paul Conn, March 9, 1971 (Box 285)
        - "Political Study of the 100th District," by John M. Engler and Thomas J. Plachta, 1970 (Box 285)
        - Post-election clips, 1990 (Box 285)
        - Press Conference to Rebut Lottery Ad, 1990 (Box 285)
        - Press Releases, 1990 (Box 285)
        - Proposal B Clippings, 1988 (Box 285)
        - Publications, 1989-1990 (Box 285)
        - Radio TV Reports, 1990 (Box 285)
        - Republican Party Information, 1988-1989 (Box 285)
        - Republican State Convention, 1990 (Box 285)
        - Ross, Doug, 1988 (Box 285)
        - School Finance Reform, 1987-1988 (Box 285)
        - Speeches, 1989-1990 (Box 285)
        - Spousal Rape, 1987-1988 (Box 285)
        - Squier, Bob--Blanchard Attack Ads, 1990 (Box 285)
        - "The State of Black Michigan 1990," Urban Affairs Programs, MSU (Box 285)
        - Substance Abuse in Michigan, 1988 (Box 285)
        - Task Force Assignments, 1988-1989 (Box 285)
        - Truscott, John campaign, 1988 (Box 285)
        - Van Regenmorter, William, 1987-1989 (Box 285)
        - Vote "B,", 1988 (Box 285)
        - Election results, 1990 (Box 285)
      - Candidacy Research: Jill Murphy, 1971-1990
        - Big Guy File, 1986-1990; 2 folders (Box 313)
        - Crime and Drugs, 1986-1990 (Box 313)
        - Engler's Statements: House Journal, 1971-1978 (Box 313)
        - Engler's Statements: Senate Journal, 1979-1990 (Box 313)
        - General Assistance Cutoff, 1984-1990 (Box 313)
        - Lauve, John, 1983-1990 (Box 313)
        - Lottery, 1990 (Box 313)
        - Opposition Research, 1985-1986 (Box 313)
        - Quote Requests, 1989-1990 (Box 313)
        - Session Days, 1990 (Box 313)
        - Taxes, Taxes, Texas, 1990 (Box 313)
        - Tax Votes, 1989 (Box 313)
        - Vote Printout, 1989-1990 (Box 313)
      - Deputy Campaign Manager LeAnne Redick (Wilson), 0.4 linear feet
        - Associated Builders and Contractors, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Attorneys, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Banks, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Blacks, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Business, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Chiropractors, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Democrats for Engler, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Dentists, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Doctors, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Ethnics, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Farmers, 1989-1990 (Box 286)
        - Hispanics, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Law Enforcement, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Nurses, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Pharmacists, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Prosecutors, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Republican Appointments, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Right to Life of Michigan, 1990 (Box 286)
        - School Superintendents, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Townships, 1990 (Box 286)
      - Katherine Reid, 0.1 linear feet
        - Binsfeld, Connie (Lieutenant Governor), 1990 (Box 286)
        - Cook, Dee (Michigan State University Board of Trustees), 1990 (Box 286)
        - DeVos, Dick (State Board of Education), 1990 (Box 286)
        - Durant, Clark (Michigan Supreme Court), 1990 (Box 286)
        - Esch, Marvin (University of Michigan Board of Regents), 1990 (Box 286)
        - Hardy, Liz (Wayne State Board of Governors), 1990 (Box 286)
        - Hughes, Judy (Michigan Supreme Court), 1990 (Box 286)
        - Kopack, Laura (Wayne State Board of Governors), 1990 (Box 286)
        - McFee, Shirley (University of Michigan Board of Regents), 1990 (Box 286)
        - Miller, Judy (Secretary of State), 1990 (Box 286)
        - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Perry, Lowell (State Board of Education), 1990 (Box 286)
        - Political Agenda Publications, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Republican Mailings, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Shingleton, Jack (Michigan State University Board of Trustees), 1990 (Box 286)
        - Taylor, Cliff (Attorney General), 1990 (Box 286)
      - Indeterminate Provenance, 0.1 linear feet
        - Campaign Finance Reports, 1989 (Box 286)
        - Promote Michigan Lawsuit, 1990; 2 folders (Box 286)
        - Republican Response to Blanchard attach re: Crime and Drugs, 1990 (Box 286)
    - Transition Team, 1990-1992; 3.3 linear feet
      The records of the "Transition Team" (3.3 lin. ft.) were created by the team led by Richard McLellan, Carol Viventi and William Whitbeck. The material is highly organized and useful to determine organization, staffing, funding and mission of the Governor's Office and Michigan state departments at the beginning of Engler's tenure. The materials from the departments were gathered through interviews with officials and employees, but while the reports contain summaries of information learned, they do not name informants.
      - General, 1972-1992; 2 linear feet
        - Articles regarding transition, 1990 (Box 286)
        - "Becoming Governor: The Transition and First Year: Reflections and Advice from Governors Elected in 1990," includes Gov. Engler's reflections, 1992 (Box 286)
        - Budget Message of the Governor 1990-1991 Fiscal Year, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Bureau of the State Lottery Survey Team Report, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Bureau of the State Lottery Transition Book, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Classified Executive Service Notebook by the Bureau of Merit Systems, of the Department of Civil Service, October 1990 (Box 286)
        - Department of Education, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Department of Management and Budget, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Environmental Reorganization, 1972; 1986 (Box 286)
        - Executive Office Salary Classes, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Governor's Office, Capitol, 1990 (Box 286)
          (Contains floor plans)
        - Governor's Office Employee Manual, undated (Box 286)
        - Governor's Office, Olds Plaza, 1990 (Box 286)
        - Governor's Residence, Lansing (Box 287)
        - Governor's Residence, Mackinac Is, 1995-1998 (Box 287)
          (Contains blueprints and floor plans, and other documents regarding its placement on the National Register of Historic Places.)
        - Information for New Governors by the National Governors' Association Office of State Services (Box 287)
        - Education, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Energy Management, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Health: Costs, Access and Federalism, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Revitalizing State Economies, 1990 (Box 287)
        - McLellan, Richard--Chronological File, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Memos from McLellan, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Michigan Department of Transportation (M-DOT) Organization Manual, 1990; 2 folders (Box 287)
        - Michigan State Government in the Decade of the 90's: Familiar Problems--New Directions, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Michigan State Police, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Office of Governor-Elect Authorization Forms, Richard D. McLellan, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Office of Governor-Elect Engler Memoranda from Staff Members, Richard D. McLellan copy, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Office of Governor-Elect John M. Engler Policy Book, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Official Transitional Memos, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Organizing the Transition and the Governor's Team: Sample Documents, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Potential Candidates for Departments and Agencies, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Powers Delegated to the Governor by Federal Statute, 1991 (Box 287)
        - Prudential-Bache Capital Funding Presentation to State of Michigan, December 18, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Selection Interview Guide by Bureau of Selection, Dept. of Civil Service, 1986 (Box 287)
        - Special Report: Great Lakes; Reengineering State Services; and Financial Services Regulation, 1990 (Box 287)
        - Transition and the New Governor: A Critical Overview," by NGA, undated (Box 288)
        - Transition Legal Team, December 29, 1990; 5 folders (Box 288)
        - Transition Staff Signed Agreements, 1990 (Box 288)
        - Transition Survey Team Background, 1990 (Box 288)
        - Viventi, Carol (Box 288)
        - Appointments Procedures, 1990 (Box 288)
        - Credit and Drug Check Procedures, 1990 (Box 288)
        - Official Transition Memoranda, 1990 (Box 288)
        - Whitbeck, William (Box 288)
        - Legal Issues Procedures, 1990 (Box 288)
        - Transition Team advice, 1990 (Box 288)
      - Transition Legal Team, 1989-1992; 1.3 linear feet
        The records of the "Transition Legal Team" were gathered and written in support of the "Report of the Transition Legal Team." Missing file numbers in the series were not transferred by the Governor's office to the Bentley Historical Library.
        - General
          - 4003 Code of Ethics, 1990-1991 (Box 288)
          - 4015 1991 Layoffs (Box 288)
          - 4039 Civil Service Commission, 1991-1992 (Box 288)
          - 4043 Temporary Layoffs, 1991 (Box 288)
          - 4055 Liquor Control Commission Privatization, 1991-1992 (Box 288)
          - 4056 Permanent Replacement of Strikers, 1991 (Box 288)
        - Negotiations
          - 6001 Department of State Police, 1991 (Box 288)
          - 6002 Department of Social Services, 1991 (Box 288)
          - 6003 Office of Services to the Aging, 1991-1992 (Box 288)
          - 6004 Department of Commerce, 1991-1992 (Box 288)
          - 6005 Department of Public Health, 1991 (Box 288)
          - 6008 Department of Labor, 1991-1992 (Box 288)
          - 6010 Overall Reorganization, 1990-1992 (Box 288)
          - 6011 Reorganization--Licensing, 1990-1991 (Box 288)
          - 6012 Reorganization--Insurance Bureau, 1991 (Box 188)
            - Accident Fund of Michigan: Background Materials on Privatization, 1991; 2 folders (Box 188)
            - Accident Fund of Michigan: Descriptive and Financial Materials, 1992 (Box 188)
            - Cadillac Insurance Co. Dispute, 1989-1991 (Box 188)
          - 6013 Reorganization--Wayne Co. Office of Child and Youth Services, 1991 (Box 188)
          - 6015 Reorganization--Corrections, 1991-1992 (Box 188)